I'm goin' down to South Park,
gonna have myself a time.
Friendly faces everywhere.
Humble folks
without temptation.
Goin' down to South Park,
gonna leave my woes behind.
Ample parking day or night.
People spouting,
"Howdy, neighbor!"
Heading on up to South Park,
gonna see if I can't unwind.
Timmy, Timmy, Timmy, Timmy.
Timmy, Timmy,
liv-a-la, Timmy!
Come on down to South Park
and meet some friends of mine.
Okay, children.
Step off the bus
and form a group
next to the nice redneck...
I mean rancher.
Hello, boys and girls.
My name is Rancher Bob.
Let's all say hello
to Rancher Bob.
Hi, Rancher Bob.
I'm pleased to show you all
the wonderful world of beef.
Follow me.
City kids get to go to museums
for field trips.
We get cow farms.
Now, out here,
you can see our cattle.
This is where the magic begins
as the cows eat, sleep,
and prepare for certain death.
They look so delicious.
Now, here we have
the slaughterhouse.
This is where we turn the cows
into steaks and burgers!
Ew!
Aw, dude!
Anybody want a free sample?
Me! Me! Me! Me!
And in here, boys and girls,
we have our veal ranch.
You see, with veal, the whole
key is keeping the cows chained
so they can't walk around
or get any exercise.
That way,
their muscle tissue stays soft
and makes for tender veal.
Wait a minute.
Veal is... little baby cows?
Yepper!
Then why the hell
do they call it "veal"?
Well, if we called it
"little baby cow",
people might not eat it.
- Yeah! I wouldn't have!
- Uh, me neither.
Oh, man!
Look at that one!
- It looks delicious!
- What?
Succulent and juicy.
Can we have a free sample
of these, too?
Well, no.
But all these veals are going
to the slaughterhouse
tomorrow morning.
They'll be steaks
by the afternoon,
and then you can buy them
at your grocery store.
All right!
Tomorrow morning?
Dude, we got to help them.
Yeah.
Psst! Cartman.
No! Uncle Jesse!
No!
Cartman, wake up!
What? What the hell
are you guys doing?
- Come on! We got to go!
- Where are we going?
We're gonna go save
the little baby cows, fat ass.
What? Why?
'Cause they're gonna get
slaughtered tomorrow, butthole!
So?
So we can't let 'em die,
douchebag.
You're our friend.
Now, come help us.
Well, in the last 3.2 seconds,
you've called me "fat ass",
"butthole", and "douchebag".
I really don't feel much
like you guys' friend.
We're sorry.
You are our friend.
We need you to help us
because friends stick together.
Wait.
I thought you said we needed him
because he has
the "Mission: Impossible
Breaking-and-Entering Playset".
Damn it, Butters.
Will you shut up?
So you need me
and my "Mission: Impossible
Breaking-and-Entering Playset".
Yes, we do.
We're those little baby cows'
only hope.
Will you help us?
Yes.
Yes, I will.
If Kyle will kiss my black ass.
What?!
Just give it a little kiss,
and I'll help.
Screw you, Cartman!
Okay, but if you want my help,
you have to give it
just a little kiss.
Kiss it.
- Go on, dude. It's the only way.
- No!
Kiss it.
Come on. Kiss it!
Just do it really fast,
and we can go.
- Have Butters kiss it.
- No. It has to be Kyle.
Oh, man!
That was so awesome!
Sick!
I felt it on my face!
Okay. Very funny, Cartman.
Now, come on.
I'm not going with you.
- Aah!
- Hey!
I don't know about this, fellas.
It says right here
on the "Mission: Impossible
Breaking-and-Entering Playset"...
"Not for actual breaking
and entering.
Breaking and entering
is a crime."
Well, killing little helpless
baby cows
should be a crime, too.
How does this thing work,
Cartman?
Jesus.
Don't you guys have any toys?
First you put on
the black ski mask
and use the torch
to cut a hole in the roof.
Okay.
That's far enough.
- I'm going to go delta.
- You have to talk louder!
I forgot the AA batteries
for the Super Talk Play-Action
headset.
I said that's far enough!
Don't be scared,
little baby cow.
We're here to set you loose.
There you go.
You're free!
Run away!
Go!
They're gonna murder you!
Stan, could you hurry it up?
I'm freezing my ass off.
You need to freeze
some of your ass off.
At least I have an ass, Jew!
What?
Come on, you stupid baby cows!
You have to get out of here!
- What's the matter?
- They aren't leaving!
See? Maybe they want to become
sweet, juicy veal steaks.
Hey, they've never been allowed
to walk before.
They just don't know how!
Oh, yeah.
They're too weak to move.
We've got to get them
out of here.
We'll keep them
at Butters' house
until they can get
their strength back.
No, no, no, no, no!
I can't bring calves
into my house.
- I'll get grounded.
- Okay. Fine, Butters.
I guess you're not
a team player.
We'll bring them to my house.
Dude, how are we gonna move
23 calves to your house?
- I don't know.
- I've got it!
We could kill Butters
and then float the calves
on a river of blood.
Don't be stupid, Cartman!
Butters doesn't have
that much blood in him.
Yeah!
I do too!
We're just gonna have to
carry them one by one.
Come on, you guys.
Check it out, you guys.
I'm calf curling.
Man, these calves
smell like crap.
I don't see how you're gonna
hide them much longer.
We won't have to.
Butters said he had something
that makes baby cows strong
again.
He's bringing it over.
Butters had that at his house?
Hey, fellas!
Butters, did you bring it?
I sure did!
We'll have those poor
baby cows in shape in no time!
All right!
"Suzanne Somers Calf Exerciser".
What?
"Makes your calves stronger
in just two days."
Oh, God damn it!
That's your plan?
You think it's a gimmick?
Suzanne promises
right on the box that it works.
Hello, Mrs. Marsh!
Officer Barbrady.
What can I do for you?
Well, we've got
a little problem.
Jed here caught your boy
and his friends
trespassing on his ranch.
They stole some of his property.
Stole?
A-Are you sure?
I followed a calf-curling trail
right to your house, ma'am.
Ooh, Stan's in trouble!
Let me kick his ass, Mom!
N-Now, my son is not a thief.
I'm sure this is just
some kind of misunderstanding.
Stanley, did you see...
Oh, crap!
Stanley, what are you doing
with those calves?
That asshole was gonna kill them
and feed them to people!
Stanley, they belong to him.
They don't belong to anybody!
Please, Mom!
We don't want these cows to die!
Let me hit him, Mom!
Stanley, this isn't up
for discussion.
The rancher is going to take
his cows back,
and you don't have a choice.
Stanley!
Stanley, open this door right
now, or you're gonna get it!
No!
Stan, you're behaving
like a kid.
You're the ones
who made me eat veal
without telling me what it was!
You're the ones who knew
we were making
little baby animals suffer!
Open this door now!
Kiss my ass!
Oh, geez.
He said "ass" to his parents.
You're getting in
pretty deep, dude.
I apologize for this,
Mister rancher person.
Why don't you just tell them
that the cows will be safe?
And when they come out,
I can take 'em back.
I can't lie to my son, okay?
If I betrayed him like that, I'd
pay for it the rest of my life.
Well, that's just too bad!
Look, that's $800
worth of veal up there,
and I have to ship it out
Friday!
What are you going to do,
Officer Barbrady?
Me?
How'd I get into this mess?
So, what happens now?
I'm gonna lock myself in here
with these cows
until we have a guarantee
of their safety in writing.
- We're with you, dude.
- Yeah!
Don't be so sure.
Because I'm gonna tell you...
This is gonna get ugly.
Real ugly.
When all is said and done,
you could all be looking
at being grounded for three,
perhaps even four weeks.
So if any of you guys want out,
just say the word now.
- I want out.
- Shut up, Cartman.
- We're with you, Stan.
- Yeah.
We can't let
those little baby cows down.
They've got no one else
to turn to.
Then it's settled.
One for all and all for one!
Except Cartman.
- Yeah!
Yeah!
Wait. What?
And so that's the situation.
Our boys have locked themselves
in Stan's room
until we can promise the calves
will live free, in writing.
Well, this is ridiculous.
I don't know how you raise
your kids,
but my son does not play
negotiator with me!
Well, excuse me, Sheila,
but it wasn't that simple.
Give me 15 seconds with Kyle,
and I'll have that door open.
Kyle, this is your mother!
You will open this door
right now!
No, I won't.
Yes.
I see what you mean, Sheila.
That was very impressive.
Kyle, if you don't do
as you're told,
I'm going to be very angry!
Well, you made me eat veal
and didn't tell me what it was!
So go ahead and be angry,
you baby-cow-killing bitch!
Very persuasive.
Aah! Open this door!
Open this door!
Oh, let... let me try.
Butters?
Butters, this is your father.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
What do I do?
Be strong, Butters.
You knew it would come to this.
Butters, answer me.
But... But Dad's a-angry at me.
Don't panic.
I'll tell you what to say.
Butters, right now!
Dad, uh, why don't you
suck my fat one?
- What?!
- Oh, sweet Jesus.
- What's gotten into them?
- All right, Stanley.
This has gone on long enough.
Your little game is over!
This isn't a game, Mom.
We're not coming out until we
know the calves will be safe.
Well, that's fine.
You boys can just stay in there
and starve to death.
Us parents are going to go
to Pizza Shack
and have pepperoni pizzas
and ice cream.
Oh, God damn it, you guys.
Cartman, stay away
from that door!
You'll have to come
out sooner or later, boys.
The longer you wait,
the more trouble you'll be in.
Round one is over.
We made it.
We didn't make it.
Your mom is right, douchebag.
What are we gonna do,
stay in here until we starve?
Our parents would never
let us starve.
They're bluffing.
This is a battle of wills.
If we hold out long enough,
they'll give in.
But we will have to sleep, dude.
Three of us can sleep
while one keeps watch.
We'll shift
every couple of hours.
Hey, this is gonna be
just like Vietnam, huh, fellas?
Whoopie!
We'll stay in this room
with these baby cows
for as long as it takes!
Well, we tried everything.
We can't get through the door
without tearing apart the house.
Dear God!
It's been over 13 hours.
Oh, but my poor little poopsie
must be getting so hungry.
Maybe we should get them
a little food.
Ms. Cartman,
this is a battle of will.
We need our boys to know that
we're not gonna cave in at all.
Oh, all right.
Let's just go to bed and
let them play their little game
for as long as they can.
- Good night, fellas!
- Good night.
Good night, Patches.
Good night, Halloway.
Good night, Neptune.
Good night, Davis.
Good night, Bud.
Good night, Red.
Good night, Paulette.
Good night, Chastity.
Butters, I'm going to kill
you over and over again.
Can't go on.
Need... food.
I didn't realize hunger
made you feel so bad.
There's only one alternative,
you guys.
We're gonna have to eat a calf.
No, Cartman,
we're not eating a calf.
All right! Then we're gonna
have to eat Butters.
He might be right, dude.
Aw, heck.
Wait.
What is that?
- Dude!
- Food!
Ms. Cartman, what are you doing?
Ooh, I just can't stand
to see my baby suffer.
Oh, dear God.
You've ruined everything!
All right!
See?
Now we can hold out for weeks!
Look, you guys!
Beef jerky!
- Yeah! And fried chicken!
- Wha...?
Dude, what are you guys doing?
We're eating, dude.
You're eating meat!
What the hell do you think
we're doing all this for?
Hey, I'm doing it
to save little baby cows.
I'm not gonna stop eating meat
altogether.
- Me neither.
- Yeah.
If you don't eat meat at all,
you become a pussy.
That's fine.
You guys can live off of flesh.
But I'm never eating meat again.
Go ahead.
That's more for us.
You want some beef jerky, buddy?
Yes.
Who's your buddy?
Who's hungry?
Who's a hungry man?
Dude, that's messed up.
You guys, check this out!
Tom, I'm standing
in front of the house
where four insane boy terrorists
have barricaded themselves
inside a room
with 23 live infant cattle.
Hey, look!
Some other kids are doing
the same thing we are!
Several attempts
to break into the room
have proven unsuccessful, Tom,
and the crisis is intensifying.
Here's what some people
had to say.
We were just sleeping,
when suddenly we heard
all the commotion.
I mean, to think
this could happen right here
in our own community.
We gave those kids everything,
and they turned into
little John Walkers.
The police chief of South Park
says that there will be no
negotiations with terrorists.
Oh, no. This is big-time
trouble now, fellas.
No.
This is exactly what we wanted.
- It is?
- Yes. Don't you see?
This validates everything
that we're doing.
If we're making the news,
this is obviously important
to people.
Tom, it looks like
I have an update.
Yes, it looks like
the boy-terrorist story
is not interesting news
to anyone.
Uh, nothing else
was going on, Tom,
so this was the only story
we had to make seem important,
but people are just simply
tuning out.
So HBC will now be
switching programming
once again to
"Puppies From Around the World"!
I don't believe it.
The Chinese puppy is my favorite
so far!
Butters?
B-Butters, you have your arm
around me!
Oh, sorry.
I thought you were Mr. Pickles.
We must help the helpless.
We must save the unsaved.
What the hell is that?
For if we fight together.
We can make sure
the road is paved.
For a brighter tomorrow...
- Hippies!
- What are they doing here?
We are with you, boys!
Your message is real
and your fight is just!
Dude, those gaywads
are on our side?
Ew!
They're all dirty.
What did I tell you, Stan?
We saved some baby cows
from being eaten,
and now we're no-good,
dirty Goddamn hippies!
Tom, the calf-terrorist standoff continues,
as now members of the FBI arrive
to put an end to the conflict.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Who's in charge here?
I am.
But I don't want to be.
Where's the negotiator?
Right here...
Glen Dumont, negotiator squad.
All right.
See what you can do.
- Dude, are you okay?
- Oh, I just feel so run down.
I don't know what's wrong
with me.
- I've got these sores.
- What is that?
- Dude, maybe we should end this.
- No!
Get me a hard line to the phone
in that house.
The terrorists already said
there's no way
they're coming out.
Don't worry.
I'm a negotiator.
It's my job to talk
to freaks like this
and bring about
a peaceful resolution
using clever psychology.
Hello?
Hello. My name is Mike.
I'm a negotiator.
Is it okay if I talk to you?
Uh, hold on.
It's some negotiator named Mike.
- What do I do?
- Don't give him anything!
- What do I say?
- Aw, give me that.
Talk to me, Mike.
I'm here to make sure
we can all end this peacefully.
You want that, right?
Sure, sure.
How about we make a trade
just to show
that we can trust each other?
What'd you have in mind?
Well, how about you send out
one of the calves?
Oh, Mike. You're breaking
my balls here, Mike.
Just one.
That's all we want.
All right.
How about this?
You guys have all the leverage,
and we have nothing.
So how about we give you
one calf...
- Cartman, no!
- Dude!
It's cool.
We'll give you one calf
if you'll give us
some guns and ammunition
of our own.
What?
I-I can't do that!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought we were talking here.
But I guess you're not
talking to me. Goodbye.
No, no. Wait.
I-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Y-You're right. What reason
do you have to trust me?
I'm just a guy from Lakewood
trying to make ends meet.
Just a blue-collar guy
like your dad.
Don't have a dad, Mike.
That's not gonna work.
Oh. All right. Some guns.
I'll see what I can do.
Okay.
Up a little.
Left a little.
Almost there.
What is that?
We're giving the boys some guns
in return for a calf.
- What?
- You're giving my baby guns?
Hey, this is a negotiation
process, okay?
Did you people go
to negotiator school?
No, you didn't!
Get 'em on the line for me.
Hello?
Okay. You see that?
I keep my end of the bargain.
All right. We'll keep ours.
We'll send out one calf.
Well, h-how about you send out
two calves?
Oh, Jesus! There's just no
talking to you, is there, Mike?
We had a deal.
Do you think I'm stupid?
Don't treat me
like I'm stupid here!
I'm sorry!
Damn it!
I'm losing them!
Okay. I'm sorry.
Just send out one calf.
Oh, no, no, no. Now you're gonna
have to get us something else.
What'd you have in mind?
A little to the left.
Okay. That's good.
A little to the right.
You're giving them a missile?!
Stand down, ma'am!
Stand down!
This is a delicate process.
I've almost earned their trust.
Stan's getting worse, you guys.
- Mike. Babe.
- How we doing?
We got a real sick kid here,
Mike.
Did you get the other things
for us?
I-I did manage to get the FDA
to officially change the word
"veal" to "tortured baby cow."
Good. Good.
But I couldn't get you
North and South Dakota.
Oh, Mike.
Breaking my balls, Mike.
Now... Now, please, can...
Can we get you to come out?
All right.
Everything has worked out.
The boys have promised
to come out
and bring the cows out
with them.
All right!
I'm sorry I doubted
your abilities, Mr. Negotiator.
- They're coming out now?
- Yes.
All we need to do in return
is get
a cattle-transporting semitruck
that will take the boys
and the cattle
to Denver International Airport,
where we will have
a fully gassed airplane
waiting to take them all
to Mexico.
What?
And they want the guy that
plays Mr. Worf on "Star Trek"
to drive the truck...
In full makeup.
Jesus Christ!
All right.
That does it!
You are, in fact,
the worst negotiator
I've ever seen in action!
All right. All right.
I'll give you that.
But in return,
I want three staples.
Get out of here!
We'll get them the semi,
and we'll get them the Worf guy
from "Star Trek."
If they see that, they'll come
out, and then we can take them.
But isn't that dishonest?
Maybe so.
But if we don't do something
soon,
there could be 50,
even 60 people
who'll have to go without veal
for dinner.
Are you prepared
to let that happen?
All right.
Where is Mr. Dorn?
I was woken up
at 3:00 in the morning,
told I had to put on makeup
and come to this town.
What the hell is going on?
I'm sorry, Mr. Dorn.
It's FBI business.
We've got terrorists making
demands, and we need your help.
This is highly unusual.
All right, boys.
We have your truck.
And we have an airplane on the
tarmac at Denver International.
And Worf?
My name is Michael Dorn.
I play a character called Worf.
Stan, it worked!
It did?
They got us a truck
and an airplane and Mr. Worf!
The calves are gonna be okay!
Pick me up.
I-I want to see.
Step back!
Tell those men to step back!
Do it!
Aw, shut up,
you friggin' hippies.
All right, Mr. Worf.
Start the engine
and put her in gear.
Oh, and you must refer to me
as "Captain".
Where am I supposed to drive to?
No, see, you must say,
"Captain, where am I supposed to
drive to?"
Captain, where am I
supposed to drive to?
You're going to back the truck
up to the door
so we can safely load in
the calves.
This whole thing is ridiculous.
"Captain, this whole thing
is ridiculous."
Captain, this whole thing
is ridiculous.
Okay!
All set!
Tom, it looks as though the terrorists
are now loading the baby cows
into the back of a semi.
This is still
very uninteresting news, Tom.
Okay, Cartman!
Step on it, Mr. Worf!
All right!
We're going!
Mexico, here we come!
Wait a minute.
They're following us!
Full speed, Mr. Worf!
We cannot keep going fast
on these icy roads.
"Captain, we cannot keep
going fast on these icy roads."
Captain, we cannot keep
going fast on these icy roads.
All right, Mr. Worf.
Then reduce speed to 45
but maintain distance
from those police cruisers.
Stan, we're almost there.
You've got to hold on.
All right. They're in front
of the cattle ranch.
Hit it!
Oh, it's a double cross!
All right, boys.
The game is over.
Get out of the truck
with your hands up.
Oh, no.
No!
What are you waiting for?
Go kill them, Worf!
I'm not killing anybody.
Some goddamn Klingon you are.
We're sorry, cows.
We tried. We tried.
All right, boys.
Just stay right there
until your parents arrive.
Can I go now?
Here you go, Mr. Rancher.
I got your cattle back for you!
Well, it doesn't matter now.
What do you mean?
In the 24 hours
since the word "veal"
was officially changed
to "little tortured baby cow,"
the market has gone dry.
Seems when people see
"little tortured baby cow"
on their menus,
they don't feel like ordering.
Really?
Damn things ain't worth spit
now.
I'll let 'em live outside
with the other cows
and live a normal life.
You hear that, Stan?
It worked!
We've shut down
the veal industry!
Stan?
He's very lucky you got him here
when you did.
He was in a very advanced state
of vaginitis.
Vaginitis?
It occurs when a person
stops eating meat.
Those sores on his skin
were actually small vaginas.
If we hadn't stopped it in time,
Stan would've eventually
just become
one great big, giant pussy.
Whoa, dude.
We've got an I.V.
of pure beef blood
pumping into Stan's veins,
and the sores are fading.
Thank God we stopped it in time.
Well, I guess
we learned something today.
It's wrong to eat veal
because the animals
are so horribly mistreated.
But if you don't eat meat at
all, you break out in vaginas.
Hear, hear.
All right, boys.
It's time to go home.
You've got some serious
grounding time to start.
- I'll say!
- Aw, we're still grounded?
But... But we... we learned
things and took up a cause.
Yes, Kyle, but you still
defied your parents.
And you need to learn that
terrorism is never the answer.
That's right. Let's get
these terrorists to their rooms.
But first maybe we can grab
some burgers.
Alright!!